Dick Clark Papers
Dick Clark Papers
- Recordings, Countdown America (CDA)
  - Show #111, Dec 12-13, 1987; 8 tapes (Oversize 67-68)
    Artist: Natalie Cole
  - Show #112, Dec 19-20, 1987; 8 tapes (Oversize 68)
    Year/source: 1987 (LP
    Artist: Christmas Songs
  - Show #113, Dec 26-27, 1987; 8 tapes (Oversize 68-69)
    Year/source: 1977, 1980, 1983, 1986 (LP
    Artist: Barry Manilow
  - Show #114, Jan 2-3, 1988; 8 tapes (Oversize 69-70)
    Artist: Best of 1987
  - Show #115, Jan 9-10, 1988; 8 tapes (Oversize 70)
    Artist: Eric Carmen
  - Show #116, Jan 16-17, 1988; 8 tapes (Oversize 70-71)
    Artist: Belinda Carlisle
  - Show #117, Jan 23-24, 1988; 8 tapes (Oversize 71)
    Artist: Sting
  - Show #118, Jan 30-31, 1988; 8 tapes (Oversize 71-72)
    Artist: Gloria Estefan
  - Show #119, Feb 6-7, 1988; 8 tapes (Oversize 72-73)
    Artist: Pet Shop Boys
  - Show #120, Feb 13-14, 1988; 8 tapes (Oversize 73)
    Artist: George Michael
  - Show #121, Feb 20-21, 1988; 8 tapes (Oversize 73-74)
    Year/source: 19xx (LP
  - Show #122, Feb 27-28, 1988; 8 tapes (Oversize 74)
  - Show #123, March 5-6, 1988; 8 tapes (Oversize 75)
    Artist: Cars
  - Show #124, March 12-13, 1988; 8 tapes (Oversize 75-76)
    Artist: Stevie Wonder
  - Show #125, March 19-20, 1988; 16 tapes; (Oversize 76-77)
    Artist: David Foster
  - Show #126, March 26-27, 1988; 16 tapes (Oversize 77-78)
    Artist: Gladys Knight & the Pips
  - Show #127, April 2-3, 1988; 16 tapes (Oversize 78-79)
    Artist: Peabo Bryson
  - Show #128, April 9-10, 1988; 16 tapes (Oversize 79-81)
    Artist: Salute to the Oscars
  - Show #129, April 16-17, 1988; 16 tapes (Oversize 81-82)
    Artist: Mike Post
  - Show #130, April 23-24, 1988; 16 tapes (Oversize 82-83)
    Artist: Billy Ocean
  - Show #131, Apr 30-May 1, 1988; 16 tapes (Oversize 83-84)
    Artist: Dionne Warwick
  - Show #132, May 7-8, 1988; 16 tapes (Oversize 84-86)
    Artist: Art Garfunkel
  - Show #133, May 14-15, 1988; 16 tapes (Oversize 86-87)
    Artist: Dan Hill
  - Show #134, May 21-22, 1988; 16 tapes (Oversize 87-88)
    Artist: Smokey Robinson
  - Show #135, May 28-29, 1988; 16 tapes (Oversize 88-89)
    Artist: James Taylor
  - Show #136, June 4-5, 1988; 16 tapes (Oversize 89-90)
    Artist: Boz Scaggs
  - Show #137, June 11-12, 1988; 16 tapes (Oversize 91-92)
  - Show #138, June 18-19, 1988; 16 tapes (Oversize 92-93)
    Artist: Bruce Hornsby & the Range
  - Show #139, June 25-26, 1988; 16 tapes (Oversize 93-94)
    Artist: Hall & Oates
  - Show #140, July 2-3, 1988; 16 tapes (Oversize 94-95)
    Artist: Debbie Gibson
  - Show #141, July 9-10, 1988; 16 tapes (Oversize 95-97)
    Artist: Richard Marx
  - Show #142, July 16-17, 1988; 16 tapes (Oversize 97-98)
    Artist: Sade
  - Show #143, July 23-24, 1988; 16 tapes (Oversize 98-99)
    Artist: Jets
  - Show #144, July 30-31, 1988; 16 tapes (Oversize 99-100)
    Artist: Chicago
  - Show #145, August 6-7, 1988; 14 tapes; lacking 3A, 3B (Oversize 100-101)
    Artist: Julio Iglesias
  - Show #146, August 13-14, 1988; 15 tapes; lacking 4B (Oversize 101-103)
    Artist: Tiffany
  - Show #147, August 20-21, 1988; 16 tapes (Oversize 103-104)
    Artist: Corey Hart
  - Show #148, August 27-28, 1988; 16 tapes (Oversize 104-105)
  - Show #149, Sept 3-4, 1988; 16 tapes (Oversize 105-106)
    Artist: Moody Blues
  - Show #150, Sept 10-11, 1988; 16[?] tapes (Oversize 106-108)
    Artist: Little River Band
  - Show #151, Sept 17-18, 1988; 16 tapes (Oversize 108-109)
  - Show #152, Sept 24-25, 1988; 16 tapes (Oversize 109-110)
    Artist: Peter Cetera
  - Show #153, Oct 1-2, 1988; 16 tapes (Oversize 110-111)
    Artist: Olivia Newton-John
  - Show #154, Oct 8-9, 1988; 16 tapes (Oversize 111-112)
    Artist: Christopher Cross
  - Show #155, Oct 15-16, 1988; 16 tapes (Oversize 113-114)
    Artist: Phil Collins
  - Show #156, Oct 22-23, 1988; 16 tapes (Oversize 114-115)
    Artist: Rod Stewart
  - Show #157, Oct 29-30, 1988; 16 tapes (Oversize 115-116)
    Artist: Eagles
  - Show #158, Nov 5-6, 1988; 16 tapes (Oversize 116)
  - Show #159, Nov 12-13, 1988; 16 tapes (Oversize 116-117)
  - Show #160, Nov 19-20, 1988; 16 tapes (Oversize 117)
  - Show #161, Nov 26-27, 1988; 9 tapes; extra 3B (Oversize 117-118)
  - Show #162, Dec 3-4, 1988; 8 tapes (Oversize 118-119)
  - Show #163, Dec 10-11, 1988; 8 tapes (Oversize 119)
  - Show #164, Dec 17-18, 1988; 8 tapes (Oversize 119-120)
  - Show #165, Dec 24-25, 1988; 8 tapes (Oversize 120)
    Artist: Neil Diamond
  - Show #166, Dec 31, 1988-Jan 1, 1989; 8 tapes (Oversize 121)
    Year/source: 1988 (LP
    Artist: Best of 1988
  - Show #167, Jan 7-8, 1989; 8 tapes (Oversize 121-122)
    Artist: Roberta Flack
  - Show #168, Jan 14-15, 1989; 8 tapes (Oversize 122)
    Year/source: unknown
    Artist: Al Jarreau
  - Show #169, Jan 21-22, 1989; 8 tapes (Oversize 122-123)
  - Show #170, Jan 28-29, 1989; 8 tapes (Oversize 123-124)
  - Show #171, Feb 4-5, 1989; 8 tapes (Oversize 124)
  - Show #172, Feb 11-12, 1989; 8 tapes (Oversize 124-125)
    Artist: Rick Astley
  - Show #173, Feb 18-19, 1989; 8 tapes (Oversize 125)
    Artist: Kenny G
  - Show #174, Feb 25-26, 1989; 8 tapes (Oversize 125-126)
  - Show #175, March 4-5, 1989; 8 tapes (Oversize 126-127)
  - Show #176, March 11-12, 1989; 8 tapes (Oversize 127)
  - Show #177, March 18-19, 1989; 8 tapes (Oversize 127-128)
  - Show #178, March 25-26, 1989; 8 tapes (Oversize 128)
  - Show #179, April 1-2, 1989; 8 tapes (Oversize 129)
    Artist: Bangles
  - Show #180, April 8-9, 1989; 8 tapes (Oversize 129-130)
  - Show #181, April 15-16, 1989; 8 tapes (Oversize 130)
    Artist: Crosby, Stills, Nash & Young
  - Show #182, April 22-23, 1989; 8 tapes (Oversize 130-131)
  - Show #183, April 29-30, 1989; 8 tapes (Oversize 131-132)
  - Show #184, May 6-7, 1989; 8 tapes (Oversize 132)
    Artist: Bette Midler
  - Show #185, May 13-14, 1989; 8 tapes (Oversize 132-133)
    Artist: Paul Carrack
  - Show #186, May 20-21, 1989; 7 tapes; lacking 4B (Oversize 133)
  - Show #187, May 27-28, 1989; 3 tapes; lacking 1A, 2A, 3A, 1B, 2B (Oversize 133-134)
  - Show #188, June 3-4, 1989; 8 tapes (Oversize 134)
    Artist: Cher
  - Show #189, June 10-11, 1989; 8 tapes (Oversize 134-135)
    Artist: John Denver
  - Show #190, June 17-18, 1989; 8 tapes (Oversize 135)
  - Show #191, June 24-25, 1989; 8 tapes (Oversize 135-136)
    Artist: Bread/David Gates
  - Show #192, July 1-2, 1989; 8 tapes (Oversize 136-137)
    Artist: Carole King
  - Show #193, July 8-9, 1989; 8 tapes (Oversize 137)
  - Show #194, July 15-16, 1989; 8 tapes (Oversize 137-138)
    Artist: Paul McCartney
  - Show #195, July 22-23, 1989; 8 tapes (Oversize 138)
  - Show #196, July 29-30, 1989; 8 tapes (Oversize 139)
    Artist: America
  - Show #197, August 5-6, 1989; 8 tapes (Oversize 139-140)
    Year/source: 1989 (LP
    Artist: 40 Biggest Hits Of The Year So Far
  - Show #198, August 12-13, 1989; 8 tapes (Oversize 140)
    Artist: Donny Osmond
  - Show #199, August 19-20, 1989; 8 tapes (Oversize 140-141)
    Artist: Gladys Knight
  - Show #200, August 26-27, 1989; 8 tapes (Oversize 141-142)
    Artist: Gloria Estefan/MSM
  - Show #201, Sept 2-3, 1989; 8 tapes (Oversize 142)
  - Show #202, Sept 9-10, 1989; 8 tapes (Oversize 142-143)
    Artist: Beach Boys
  - Show #203, Sept 16-17, 1989; 8 tapes (Oversize 143)
  - Show #204, Sept 23-24, 1989; 8 tapes (Oversize 143-144)
    Artist: Jackson Browne
  - Show #205, Sept 30-Oct 1, 1989; 8 tapes (Oversize 144-145)
    Artist: Kenny Rogers
  - Show #206, Oct 7-8, 1989; 8 tapes (Oversize 145)
    Artist: Captain & Tennille
  - Show #207, Oct 14-15, 1989; 8 tapes (Oversize 145-146)
    Year/source: 1988 (M)
  - Show #208, Oct 21-22, 1989; 8 tapes (Oversize 146)
    Artist: Tony Orlando & Dawn
  - Show #209, Oct 28-29, 1989; 8 tapes (Oversize 147)
    Artist: Ambrosia
  - Show #210, Nov 4-5, 1989; 8 tapes (Oversize 147-148)
    Artist: Jefferson Starship
  - Show #211, Nov 11-12, 1989; 8 tapes (Oversize 148)
    Artist: Poco
  - Show #212, Nov 18-19, 1989; 8 tapes (Oversize 148-149)
    Artist: Linda Ronstadt
  - Show #213, Nov 25-26, 1989; 8 tapes (Oversize 149-150)
  - Show #214, Dec 2-3, 1989; 8 tapes (Oversize 150)
  - Show #215, Dec 9-10, 1989; 8 tapes (Oversize 150-151)
  - Show #216, Dec 16-17, 1989; 8 tapes (Oversize 151)
  - Show #217, Dec 23-24, 1989; 8 tapes (Oversize 151-152)
    Artist: Top 40 Hits of 1989
  - Show #218, Dec 30-31, 1989; 8 tapes (Oversize 152-153)
    Year/source: 1980s (LP
    Artist: Top 40 Hits of the Decade (1980’s
  - Show #219, Jan 6-7, 1990; 8 tapes (Oversize 153)
    Artist: Melissa Manchester
  - Show #220, Jan 13-14, 1990; 8 tapes (Oversize 153-154)
    Year/source: 1987 (M)
  - Show #221, Jan 20-21, 1990; 8 tapes (Oversize 154)
  - Show #222, Jan 27-28, 1990; 8 tapes (Oversize 155)
  - Show #223, Feb 3-4, 1990; 8 tapes (Oversize 155-156)
  - Show #224, Feb 10-11, 1990; 8 tapes (Oversize 156)
  - Show #225, Feb 17-18, 1990; 8 tapes (Oversize 156-157)
  - Show #226, Feb 24-25, 1990; 8 tapes (Oversize 157-158)
    Artist: Michael Bolton
  - Show #227, March 3-4, 1990; 8 tapes (Oversize 158)
  - Show #228, March 10-11, 1990; 8 tapes (Oversize 158-159)
    Artist: Billy Joel
  - Show #229, March 17-18, 1990; 8 tapes (Oversize 159)
  - Show #230, March 24-25, 1990; 8 tapes (Oversize 159-160)
  - Show #231, Mar 31-Apr 1, 1990; 8 tapes (Oversize 160-161)
  - Show #232, April 7-8, 1990; 8 tapes (Oversize 161)
    Artist: Tina Turner
  - Show #233, April 14-15, 1990; 8 tapes (Oversize 161-162)
  - Show #234, April 21-22, 1990; 8 tapes (Oversize 162)
    Artist: Janet Jackson
  - Show #235, April 28-29, 1990; 8 tapes (Oversize 163)
  - Show #236, May 5-6, 1990; 8 tapes (Oversize 163-164)
  - Show #237, May 12-13, 1990; 8 tapes (Oversize 164)
    Artist: Tears For Fears
  - Show #238, May 19-20, 1990; 7 tapes; lacking 2A (Oversize 164-165)
    Artist: Basia
  - Show #239, May 26-27, 1990; 8 tapes (Oversize 165)
    Artist: Ronald Isley/Isley Brothers
  - Show #240, June 2-3, 1990; 8 tapes (Oversize 166)
  - Show #241, June 9-10, 1990; 8 tapes (Oversize 166-167)
  - Show #242, June 16-17, 1990; 8 tapes (Oversize 167)
  - Show #243, June 23-24, 1990; 8 tapes (Oversize 167-168)
  - Show #244, Jun 30-July 1, 1990; 8 tapes (Oversize 168-169)
  - Show #245, July 7-8, 1990; 8 tapes (Oversize 169)
    Artist: Taylor Dayne
  - Show #246, July 14-15, 1990; 8 tapes (Oversize 169-170)
  - Show #247, July 21-22, 1990; 8 tapes (Oversize 170)
    Artist: James Ingram
  - Show #248, July 28-29, 1990; 8 tapes (Oversize 170-171)
  - Show #249, August 4-5, 1990; 8 tapes (Oversize 171-172)
    Year/source: 1982 (M)
  - Show #250, August 11-12, 1990; 8 tapes (Oversize 172)
  - Show #251, August 18-19, 1990; 8 tapes (Oversize 172-173)
  - Show #252, August 25-26, 1990; 8 tapes (Oversize 173)
    Artist: Patti Austin
  - Show #253, Sept 1-2, 1990; 8 tapes (Oversize 174)
    Artist: Dion DiMucci
  - Show #254, Sept 8-9, 1990; 8 tapes (Oversize 174-175)
  - Show #255, Sept 15-16, 1990; 7 tapes; lacking 4A (Oversize 175)
  - Show #256, Sept 22-23, 1990; 8 tapes (Oversize 175-176)
  - Show #257, Sept 29-30, 1990; 8 tapes (Oversize 176)
    Artist: Santana
  - Show #258, Oct 6-7, 1990; 8 tapes (Oversize 177)
    Artist: John Lennon
  - Show #259, Oct 13-14, 1990; 8 tapes (Oversize 177-178)
  - Show #260, Oct 20-21, 1990; 8 tapes (Oversize 178)
    Artist: Righteous Brothers
  - Show #261, Oct 27-28, 1990; 8 tapes (Oversize 178-179)
    Artist: Breathe
  - Show #262, Nov 3-4, 1990; 8 tapes (Oversize 179-180)
  - Show #263, Nov 10-11, 1990; 8 tapes (Oversize 180)
  - Show #264, Nov 17-18, 1990; 8 tapes (Oversize 180-181)
  - Show #265, Nov 24-25, 1990; 8 tapes (Oversize 181)
  - Show #266, Dec 1-2, 1990; 8 tapes (Oversize 181-182)
    Artist: Judy Collins
  - Show #267, Dec 8-9, 1990; 8 tapes (Oversize 182-183)
  - Show #268, Dec 15-16, 1990; 8 tapes (Oversize 183)
  - Show #269, Dec 22-23, 1990; 8 tapes (Oversize 183-184)
  - Show #270, Dec 29-30, 1990; 8 tapes (Oversize 184)
    Year/source: 1990 (LP)s
    Artist: Year End Part 1
  - Show #91-1/271, Jan 5-6, 1991; 8 tapes (Oversize 185)
    Year/source: 1990 (LP
    Artist: Year End Part 2
  - Show #91-2/272, Jan 12-13, 1991; 8 tapes (Oversize 185-186)
  - Show #91-3/273, Jan 19-20, 1991; 8 tapes (Oversize 186)
  - Show #91-4/274, Jan 26-27, 1991; 8 tapes (Oversize 186-187)
    Artist: Styx
  - Show #91-5/275, Feb 2-3, 1991; 8 tapes (Oversize 187-188)
  - Show #91-6/276, Feb 9-10, 1991; 8 tapes (Oversize 188)
    Artist: Air Supply
  - Show #91-7/277, Feb 16-17, 1991; 8 tapes (Oversize 188-189)
  - Show #92-3/325, Jan 18-19, 1992; 8 tapes (Oversize 189)
    Year/source: 82/87/91 (CD)
  - Show #92-4/326, Jan 25-26, 1992; 8 tapes (Oversize 189)
  - Show #92-5/327, Feb 1-2, 1992; 8 tapes (Oversize 189)
    Artist: Linda Rondstadt
  - Show #92-6/328, Feb 8-9, 1992; 8 tapes (Oversize 190)
    Year/source: 77/82/87/91 (CD)
  - Show #92-7/329, Feb 15-16, 1992; 8 tapes (Oversize 190)
    Year/source: 82/87/91 (M)
  - Show #92-8/330, Feb 22-23, 1992; 8 tapes (Oversize 190)
  - Show #92-9/331, Feb 29-Mar 1, 1992; 8 tapes (Oversize 190)
  - Show #92-10/332, March 7-8, 1992; 8 tapes (Oversize 190-191)
  - Show #92-11/333, March 14-15, 1992; 8 tapes (Oversize 191)
  - Show #92-12/334, March 21-22, 1992; 8 tapes (Oversize 191)
  - Show #92-13/335, March 28-29, 1992; 8 tapes (Oversize 191)
    Artist: Michael Jackson
  - Show #92-14/336, April 4-5, 1992; 8 tapes (Oversize 191)
  - Show #92-15/337, April 11-12, 1992; 8 tapes (Oversize 192)
    Artist: Aaron Neville
  - Show #92-16/338, April 18-19, 1992; 8 tapes (Oversize 192)
  - Show #92-17/339, April 25-26, 1992; 8 tapes (Oversize 192)
  - Show #92-18/340, May 2-3, 1992; 8 tapes (Oversize 192)
    Artist: Bruce Springsteen
  - Show #92-19/341, May 9-10, 1992; 8 tapes (Oversize 193)
    Artist: Luther Vandross
  - Show #92-20/342, May 16-17, 1992; 8 tapes (Oversize 193)
    Artist: Mariah Carey
  - Show #92-21/343, May 23-24, 1992; 8 tapes (Oversize 193)
    Artist: Paula Abdul
  - Show #92-22/344, May 30-31, 1992; 8 tapes (Oversize 193)
    Artist: Amy Grant
  - Show #92-23/345, June 6-7, 1992; 8 tapes (Oversize 193-194)
  - Show #92-24/346, June 13-14, 1992; 8 tapes (Oversize 194)
    Artist: Genesis
  - Show #92-25/347, June 20-21, 1992; 8 tapes (Oversize 194)
    Artist: Lionel Richie
  - Show #92-26/348, June 27-28, 1992; 8 tapes (Oversize 194)
  - Show #92-27/349, July 4-5, 1992; 8 tapes (Oversize 194)
  - Show #92-28/350, July 11-12, 1992; 8 tapes (Oversize 195)
    Artist: Madonna
  - Show #92-29/351, July 18-19, 1992; 8 tapes (Oversize 195)
    Artist: Loggins & Messina
  - Show #92-30/352, July 25-26, 1992; 8 tapes (Oversize 195)
  - Show #92-31/353, August 1-2, 1992; 8 tapes (Oversize 195)
  - Show #92-32/354, August 8-9, 1992; 8 tapes (Oversize 196)
  - Show #92-33/355, August 15-16, 1992; 8 tapes (Oversize 196)
  - Show #92-34/356, August 22-23, 1992; 8 tapes (Oversize 196)
  - Show #92-35/357, August 29-30, 1992; 8 tapes (Oversize 196)
    Year/source: 77/82/87/91 (M)
  - Show #92-35/358, Sept 5-6, 1992; 8 tapes (Oversize 196-197)
  - Show #92-36/359, Sept 12-13, 1992; 8 tapes (Oversize 197)
  - Show #92-37/360, Sept 19-20, 1992; 8 tapes (Oversize 197)
  - Show #92-38/361, Sept 26-27, 1992; 8 tapes (Oversize 197)
  - Show #92-39/362, Oct 3-4, 1992; 8 tapes (Oversize 197-198)
  - Show #92-40/363, Oct 10-11, 1992; 8 tapes (Oversize 198)
  - Show #92-41/364, Oct 17-18, 1992; 8 tapes (Oversize 198)
  - Show #92-42/365, Oct 24-25, 1992; 8 tapes (Oversize 198)
  - Show #92-43/366, Oct 31-Nov 1, 1992; 8 tapes (Oversize 198-199)
  - Show #92-44/367, Nov 7-8, 1992; 8 tapes (Oversize 199)
  - Show #92-45/368, Nov 14-15, 1992; 8 tapes (Oversize 199)
  - Show #92-46/369, Nov 21-22, 1992; 8 tapes (Oversize 199)
  - Show #92-47/370, Nov 28-29, 1992; 8 tapes (Oversize 199)
  - Show #92-48/371, Dec 5-6, 1992; 8 tapes (Oversize 200)
  - Show #92-49/372, Dec 12-13, 1992; 8 tapes (Oversize 200)
  - Show #92-51/374, Dec 26-27, 1992; 8 tapes (Oversize 200)
    Year/source: 1992 (CD)
    Artist: Best of 1992, Part 1
  - Show #93-1/375, Jan 2-3, 1993; 8 tapes (Oversize 200-201)
    Year/source: 1992
  - Show #93-2/376, Jan 9-10, 1993; 8 tapes (Oversize 201)
    Year/source: 78/83/88/92 (CD)
    Artist: Celine Dion
  - Show #93-3/377, Jan 16-17, 1993; 8 tapes (Oversize 201)
  - Show #93-4/378, Jan 23-24, 1993; 8 tapes (Oversize 201)
  - Show #93-5/379, Jan 30-31, 1993; 8 tapes (Oversize 201-202)
  - Show #93-6/380, Feb 6-7, 1993; 8 tapes (Oversize 202)
  - Show #93-7/381, Feb 13-14, 1993; 8 tapes (Oversize 202)
  - Show #93-8/382, Feb 20-21, 1993; 8 tapes (Oversize 202)
  - Show #93-9/383, Feb 27-28, 1993; 8 tapes (Oversize 202)
  - Show #93-10/384, March 6-7, 1993; 8 tapes (Oversize 203)
  - Show #93-11/385, March 13-14, 1993; 8 tapes (Oversize 203)
  - Show #93-12/386, March 20-21, 1993; 8 tapes (Oversize 203)
  - Show #93-13/387, March 27-28, 1993; 8 tapes (Oversize 203)
  - Show #93-15/389, April 10-11, 1993; 6 tapes; 2 copies (Oversize 203-204)
  - Show #93-16/390, April 17-18, 1993; 3 tapes (Oversize 204)
  - Show #93-17/391, April 24-25, 1993; 3 tapes (Oversize 204)
  - Show #93-18/392, May 1-2, 1993; 3 tapes (Oversize 204-205)
    Year/source: 83/88/92 (CD)
    Artist: Wilson Phillips
  - Show #93-19/393, May 8-9, 1993; 3 tapes (Oversize 205)
  - Show #93-20/394, May 15-16, 1993; 3 tapes (Oversize 205)
    Artist: Bruce Hornsby
  - Show #93-21/395, May 22-23, 1993; 3 tapes (Oversize 205)
  - Show #93-22/396, May 29-30, 1993; 3 tapes (Oversize 205)
  - Show #93-23/397, June 5-6, 1993; 3 tapes (Oversize 206)
  - Show #93-24/398, June 12-13, 1993; 3 tapes (Oversize 206)
  - Show #93-26/400, June 26-27, 1993; 3 tapes (Oversize 206)
  - Show #93-27/401, July 3-4, 1993; 3 tapes (Oversize 206-207)
  - Show #93-28/402, July 10-11, 1993; 3 tapes (Oversize 207)
  - Show #93-29/403, July 17-18, 1993; 3 tapes (Oversize 207)
  - Show #93-30/404, July 24-25, 1993; 3 tapes (Oversize 207)
  - Show #93-31/405, July 31-Aug 1, 1993; 3 tapes (Oversize 207-208)
  - Show #93-32/406, August 7-8, 1993; 3 tapes (Oversize 208)
  - Show #93-33/407, August 14-15, 1993; 3 tapes (Oversize 208)
  - Show #93-34/408, August 21-22, 1993; 3 tapes (Oversize 208)
  - Show #93-35/409, August 28-29, 1993; 3 tapes (Oversize 208)
  - Show #93-26/410, Sept 4-5, 1993; 3 tapes (Oversize 209)
    Year/source: T?
  - Show #93-27/411, Sept 11-12, 1993; 3 tapes (Oversize 209)
  - Show #93-28/412, Sept 18-19, 1993; 3 tapes (Oversize 209)
  - Show #93-39/413, Sept 25-26, 1993; 3 tapes (Oversize 209)
    Year/source: 78/83/88/92 (T?/CD)
  - Show #93-40/414, Oct -2-3, 1993; 3 tapes (Oversize 209-210)
  - Show #93-41/415, Oct 9-10, 1993; 3 tapes (Oversize 210)
  - Show #93-42/416, Oct 16-17, 1993; 3 tapes (Oversize 210)
  - Show #93-43/417, Oct 23-24, 1993; 3 tapes (Oversize 210)
    Year/source: 83/88/92 (T?/CD)
  - Show #93-44/418, Oct 30-31, 1993; 3 tapes (Oversize 210)
    Year/source: 83/88/92 (T?CD)
  - Show #93-45/419, Nov 6-7, 1993; 3 tapes (Oversize 211)
  - Show #93-46/420, Nov 13-14, 1993; 3 tapes (Oversize 211)
  - Show #93-47/421, Nov 20-21, 1993; 3 tapes (Oversize 211)
  - Show #93-48/422, Nov 27-28, 1993; 3 tapes (Oversize 211)
  - Show #93-49/423, Dec 4-5, 1993; 3 tapes (Oversize 212)
  - Show #93-50/424, Dec 11-12, 1993; 3 tapes (Oversize 212)
  - Show #93-51/425, Dec 18-19, 1993; 3 tapes (Oversize 212)
    Year/source: X-Mas Flashback (T?/CD)
  - Show #93-52/426, Dec 25-26, 1993; 3 tapes (Oversize 212)
  - Show #94-01/427, Jan 1-2, 1994; 3 tapes (Oversize 212-213)
    Year/source: 1993 (CD)
    Artist: 1993 Year End Part #1
  - Show #94-02/428, Jan 8-9, 1994; 3 tapes (Oversize 213)
    Year/source: 1993 (M)
    Artist: 1993 Year End Part #2
  - Show #94-03/429, Jan 15-16, 1994; 3 tapes (Oversize 213)
    Year/source: 84/89/93 (CD)
  - Show #94-04/430, Jan 22-23, 1994; 3 tapes (Oversize 213)
  - Show #94-05/431, Jan 29-30, 1994; 3 tapes (Oversize 213-214)
  - Show #94-06/432, Feb 5-6, 1994; 3 tapes (Oversize 214)
  - Show #94-07/433, Feb 12-13, 1994; 3 tapes (Oversize 214)
    Artist: Bryan Adams
  - Additional shows in process
- Recordings, Dick Clark in Hollywood (DCIH)
  Ninety-second spots, interviews with actors, directors, etc. Interviewees include Olympia Dukakis, Christian Slater, Sandra Bullock, Bruce Willis, Peter Reckell, Alan Alda, and more.
  In process, 511 episodes.
- Recordings, Dick Clark's Music Machine (DCMM)
  In process, 79 shows.
- Recordings, Dick Clark's National Music Survey (NMS)
  In process, 231 shows.
- Recordings, Dick Clark's Solid Gold (DCSG)
  In process, 351 shows.
- Recordings, Dick Clark's U.S. Music Survey (USMS)
  Successor to Countdown America. Featured artists include Chicago, Elton John, Amy Grant, Styx, Boyz II Men, Bonnie Raitt, more. Year-end shows were usually a "Best of" compilation.
  In process, 364 shows.
- Recordings, Rock, Roll and Remember (RRR)
  All shows consists of 5 tapes, labeled A through E. "A" reels are the voice tracks. The remainder, B-E, reference the first through 4th hours.
  Notable dates: Show #98-5 is the beginning of rebroadcast RRR (RRR Classic). No remixing occurred in these shows. The jingle package was changed on 6-27-95. Also in 1995, the numbering of shows changes from a purely sequential number to the year followed by week (example: 95-01 is the first show for 1995). Show #491 (July 6-7, 1991) was the first show issued to radio stations on CD. In early 2002 (show 2002-11), CDs replaced tape as the media for mastering the show. Show #08-41 was the last for which a radio station master was sent out; after that, radio stations downloaded the show from a website.
  - Shows #1 - #99 - in process
  - Show #100, Jan 7-8, 1984; 5 tapes (Oversize 214)
    Year/source: 1967 (T/LP)
    Artist: Brook Benton
  - Show #101, Jan 14-15, 1984; 5 tapes (Oversize 214-215)
    Year/source: 1975 (T)
    Artist: Little Richard
  - Show #102, Jan 21-22, 1984; 5 tapes (Oversize 215)
    Year/source: 1961 (T/LP)
  - Show #103, Jan 28-29, 1984; 5 tapes (Oversize 215-216)
    Year/source: 1968 (T)
    Artist: Anne Murray
  - Show #104, Feb 4-5, 1984; 5 tapes (Oversize 216)
    Year/source: 1959 (T/LP)
    Artist: Marvin Gaye
  - Show #105, Feb 11-12, 1984; 5 tapes (Oversize 216)
    Year/source: 1965 (T/LP)
  - Show #106, Feb 18-19, 1984; 5 tapes (Oversize 216-217)
    Year/source: 1960 (T/LP)
    Artist: Association
  - Show #107, Feb 25-26, 1984; 5 tapes (Oversize 217)
    Year/source: 1972 (T)
    Artist: Mary Wells
  - Show #108, March 3-4, 1984; 5 tapes (Oversize 217)
    Year/source: 1969 (T/LP)
    Artist: Jackie Wilson
  - Show #109, March 10-11, 1984; 5 tapes (Oversize 218)
    Year/source: 1962 (T/LP)
    Artist: Searchers
  - Show #110, March 17-18, 1984; 5 tapes (Oversize 218)
    Year/source: 1958 (T/LP)
    Artist: Seals & Crofts
  - Show #111, March 24-25, 1984; 5 tapes (Oversize 218-219)
    Year/source: 1974 (T/LP)
    Artist: Temptations
  - Show #112, Mar 31- Ap 1, 1984; 5 tapes (Oversize 219)
    Year/source: 1966 (T/LP)
    Artist: Bread
  - Show #113, April 7-8, 1984; 5 tapes (Oversize 219)
    Year/source: 1975 (T/LP)
    Artist: Monkees
  - Show #114, April 14-15, 1984; 5 tapes (Oversize 219-220)
    Year/source: 1964 (T/LP)
  - Show #115, April 21-22, 1984; 5 tapes (Oversize 220)
    Year/source: 1970 (T/LP)
    Artist: Peter, Paul & Mary
  - Show #116, April 28-29, 1984; 5 tapes (Oversize 220-221)
    Year/source: 1957 (T/LP)
    Artist: Paul Revere & the Raiders
  - Show #117, May 5-6, 1984; 5 tapes (Oversize 221)
    Year/source: 1971 (T/LP)
    Artist: Supremes
  - Show #118, May 12-13, 1984; 5 tapes (Oversize 221)
    Year/source: 1976 (T/LP)
    Artist: Duane Eddy
  - Show #119, May 19-20, 1984; 5 tapes (Oversize 221-222)
    Artist: Stylistics
  - Show #120, May 26-27, 1984; 5 tapes (Oversize 222)
    Year/source: 1963 (T/LP)
  - Show #121, June 2-3, 1984; 5 tapes (Oversize 222)